原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     吃冰棒   小酸奶   程程Tara
翻译     Lynn_宁   一只虾
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     今   大葱
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
双峰
第三季  第九集
谢谢你  塔米
Thank you, Tammy.
不客气
You're welcome.
办公室转来一通电话
Patched in through the office,
是戴维斯上校从五角大楼打来找你的
it's a Colonel Davis for you at the Pentagon.
紧急电话
Urgent.
小声一点
Try to keep your voice down.
什么
What?
喂
Hello?
上校
Colonel?
什么情况
What have you got?
我一点儿也不喜欢你的措辞  上校
I don't appreciate your language one bit, Colonel.
一个地方
Oh, a place.
鹿角镇
Buckhorn.
南达科他州的鹿角镇
Buckhorn, South Dakota.
南达科他州西部
West South Dakota.
天呐  我们现在在南达科他州东部上方
Well, by golly, we're over east South Dakota right now.
帮我记下来
Take this down.
稍等
Hold on.
大写的K
Capital K,
小写N
small N,
小写O
small O,
小写X
small X,
诺克斯
Knox.
诺克斯中尉
Lieutenant Knox.
鹿角镇警局
Buckhorn Police Department.
好了
All right.
谢谢你  上校
Thank you, Colonel.
你好啊  搭档
Hey, partner.
我们以为你昨晚就会到
We was expecting you last night.
看起来你一直在流血
Looks like you're been spilling.
这个地方归谁所有
Who owns this establishment?
农民
Farmers.
他们人呢
Where are they?
他们在外面睡觉
Oh, they're sleeping out back.
你需要什么
What you need?
几部干净的手机
A couple clean phones.
弄点它的子弹
And something for this.
先别管这个了
Well, fuck that.
我给你找把好枪
I'll get you some real nice puppies and biscuits.
香塔尔
Hey, Chantal.
老板来了
Boss man's here.
把工具拿出来
Grab the kit.
他受伤了吗
Is he hurt?
操
Shit.
我们等了你一晚上
We was waiting for you all night.
打中哪了
Where're they get you?
还好你走运
Looks like you was lucky.
我去拿工具
I'll get the kit.
到里面去
Go on inside.
你看我们能不能先不直接回费城
Rather than return directly to Philadelphia,
介不不介意我们去一趟
would you mind if we made a short trip
南科达州的鹿角镇
to Buckhorn, South Dakota?
这事挺重要的
It's quite important.
去你妈的  戈登  我想回家
Fuck you, Gordon. I want to go home.
事关重大
This is important,
你也会感兴趣的  戴安
and it could be of interest to you, Diane.
一个老案子  涉及一个
An old case involving a man
库柏特工曾经认识的人
Agent Cooper once knew.
蓝玫瑰案
The Blue Rose case.
是的
Yes.
马上给你送来
Coming up.
我得先去跟机长说下
Got to talk to the pilot first.
计划有变
There're been a change of plan.
我们要去南科达州的鹿角镇
We're going over to Buckhorn, South Dakota.
我知道你要说什么
I know.
我知道  "去你妈的  艾伯特"
I know. "Fuck you, Albert."
已被屏蔽
我是普雷斯顿探员
Agent Preston.
好
Good.
我明白了  我叫他接
Yes, I understand. I'll get him.
是墨菲典狱长
It's Warden Murphy.
墨菲典狱长
Warden Murphy?
你们的库柏越狱了
Your man Cooper escaped.
什么
What?
怎么会这样
How the hell did that happen?
库柏越狱了
Cooper flew the coop.
晚饭时的谈话气氛很活跃
发送
你动手了吗
Did you do it?
还没有
Not yet.
最好下次我打电话来时已经搞定了
Better be done next time I call.
罗杰  进来
Roger, come in here.
这个行吗  老板
How's that, boss?
真的挺不错的  哈齐
It's real good, Hutch.
好
All right.
我要你接下来两天内杀了典狱长
I want you to kill a warden within the next two days.
典狱长
A warden?
行
All right.
你要香塔尔在我动手之前跟他鬼混一下吗
You want Chantal to mess with him before I come?
他会玩得很尽兴的
He'll sing for me.
随你们吧
Whatever you want.
我给你们在拉斯维加斯弄了一辆双车头火车
Then I got a doubleheader for you in Vegas.
那就开双头
Oh, let's play two.
做掉典狱长后我会把详细情况短信给你
I'll text you details after you do the warden.
记住
Remember this.
扬克顿联邦监狱的墨菲典狱长
Warden Murphy, Yankton Federal Prison.
在他家  或是上班的地方
Kill him at home, at work,
或是上班路上把他杀了
or on the way.
好
Okay.
香塔尔
Hey, Chantal,
给老板一个湿吻
give the boss man a wet one.
真希望可以继续
I wish it was more.
以后一定补上
I'll take a rain check.
没问题  亲爱的
You got it, sweetheart.
销毁这部手机
Kill that phone.
把这里清理干净
And clear out of this place.
主路在那边
The main road is that way.
拉斯维加斯警局
他惹过什么麻烦吗
He ever give any problems?
没有  道吉从来不给我惹麻烦
No, I never had any trouble with Dougie at all.
他是个  好市民
He's a... solid citizen.
所以你不知道为什么
So you can't think of any reason
会有人想杀他
why someone would try to kill him.
我想不出原因
Not off the top of my head.
当然  在保险业中
Of course, in the insurance business,
如果有人事不遂愿
folks have been known to hold a grudge
难免会心存嫉恨
if things don't go their way.
通常都是为了钱  布什内尔
It's usually about money, Bushnell.
简单纯粹
Pure and simple.
也不需要什么其它原因了
Nobody needs more reason than that.
他是什么来头
So what's his background?
他在你手下做事做了多久了
How long has he been with you?
已经十二年了
Twelve years now.
他是个好雇员
He's a good worker.
他做事慢条斯理
He's slow, steady.
我看重点在"慢"吧
Little more emphasis on the "slow."
据我所知  道吉出了一场车祸
Dougie had a car accident, as I recall,
那是在他来我这上班不久前
not long before he came to work for me.
他偶尔
Every once in a while,
还会出现一些后遗症
he shows some lingering effects.
他妻子应该比我更了解情况
His wife can talk to that better than I can.
那...
Well...
很感谢你过来一趟  布什内尔
we appreciate you coming down, Bushnell.
很感谢你们的帮助
Well, I really appreciate your help.
这事还真蹊跷
Damn strange business.
先是他的车爆炸了
First his car blows up,
然后又有人想杀他
and then somebody tries to kill him.
我们一有进展就会通知你的
We'll get back to you as soon as we have something.
道吉  你今天休息吧
Dougie, you can take the rest of the day off.
太好了  这样我就能带他去医院了
Well, that's great, because I can take him to the doctor.
从明天起
Starting tomorrow,
你和我一起做事
you and I are gonna work together
研究下到底是怎么回事
and get some answers.
怎么回事
Answers.
看看这个
So get this.
这里什么都没有  一片空白
There is nothing, and I mean nothing,
道格拉斯先生1997年前的记录
on our Mr. Douglas Jones prior to 1997.
不可能吧
You're shitting me.
没有驾照信息
No driver's license.
护照信息  社保信息
No passport. No social.
没有学校记录  缴税记录
Class records. Tax records.
也没有出生证明
No birth certificate.
见了鬼了
I'll be damned.
证人保护计划吗
Witness protection?
也许
Maybe.
你认识那人还在法院吗
You still got that guy at Justice?
我让他查查
I'll run it by him.
车尾灯修了吗
Did you get that taillight fixed?
修个破车尾灯居然要239块
To the tune of 239 bucks for a fuckin' taillight.
肯定是个美女
Must be a beauty.
还记得那个拿把钳子的澳大利亚小伙吗
Remember the Australian guy with the pliers?
要不我们跟他再说说
Should we talk to him again?
就像跟狗讲话一样
It's like talking to a dog.
她还会嚷嚷个不停
And she does all the barking.
我有个主意
I have an idea.
给你一杯新鲜咖啡  琼斯先生
Brought you a fresh one, Mr. Jones.
你要不要来一杯  女士
Can I get you one too, madam?
不用了  谢谢
Oh, no, thanks,
但还是谢谢你给道吉送了一杯
but thanks for bringing one for Dougie.
懂
Yeah.
到手
Got ya.
福斯科斯
Hey, Fuscos?
什么事
Yes?
警官
Sergeant.
来得正好
Just in time.
请查下指纹和DNA
Prints and DNA, please.
我来的目的是想告诉你
Hey, I was just coming to tell you
那些掌印是从枪上收集到的
that those palm prints came back off that gun.
我们的老朋友艾克穗
Our old friend Ike the Spike...
我们在监控着他
and we just got a 20 on him
在赌场附近的旅馆
at an off-Strip motel.
艾克穗终于自食其果了
Ike the Spike finally fucked himself.
就跟他玩玩
Hey, let him join the fun.
军士  放琼斯走吧
Sarge, let the Joneses go.
我要先把这个登记好
I got to log this first.
好吧
All right.
看
Hey, look.
是不是这辆
The right one?
对的
Yeah, right.
伙计看看那里  有条刮痕
Look, there is a scratch right there, buddy.
好了  随它吧
All right, let it go.
汽车旅馆
给JT的消息
Message for JT.
一直在打你电话
Been trying your cell.
没人接  所以试试这号码
No luck, so trying this line.
听着
Here is the message.
不要雪茄
No cigar.
在请病假
Taking medical leave.
请你告诉我他还在里面
Oh, please tell me he is still here.
他在里面的  对吧
Is he in there?
好了  向我这边
All right, towards me.
他正走去你那边
He is coming your way.
艾  你因杀人未遂
Ike, you are under arrest
要被逮捕
for attempted murder.
我们有你的掌印作为证据
We have your palm print.
事实上  艾
As a matter of fact, Ike,
我们有你的整个手掌
we have your whole palm.
双峰镇警察局
安迪  我真的很喜欢那米色的椅子
Andy, I really love the beige chair.
露西  我也超喜欢那红色的椅子
And, Lucy, I really love the red chair.
我真的非常喜欢米色的椅子  安迪
And I really love the beige chair, Andy.
好吧  亲爱的
I am sorry, pumpkin.
你买米色的椅子吧
You can get the beige chair.
已将货物放入购物车  下一步
谢谢惠顾
玛丽  你在做什么
Mary, what are you doing?
谁让他出去的
Who let him out?
他去哪了
Where is he?
约翰尼
Johnny!
约翰尼  你在哪
Johnny, where are you?
约翰尼
Johnny!
Johnny.
约翰尼
Johnny!
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
天啊
约翰尼
Johnny.
母亲
Ma?
博比  怎么了
Hey, Bobby, what's up?
-你要喝咖啡吗  -不了  谢谢
- You want some coffee? - Oh, no, thanks.
我是跟同事一起来的
I am here with the fellas.
我们要跟你谈谈
We need to talk to you.
我要问你一些问题
I need to ask you some questions.
没问题
Okay.
进来吧  伙计们
Come on in, fellas.
布里格斯夫人
Mrs. Briggs.
夫人
Ma'am.
先生们
Gentlemen.
我们来是想问问你
We are here to talk to you about Agent Cooper's visit
关于那天库柏探员来探访的事情
with the Major the day...
加兰德去世前一天
The day before Garland died.
是的
Yes.
好吧  请听我说
All right, listen to me.
那天库柏探员离开之后
Right after Agent Cooper left that day,
加兰德把我拉到一边
Garland pulled me aside,
然后他跟我说  有一天
and he said that one day...
我们的儿子博比
our son Bobby,
霍克
and Hawk,
还有杜鲁门警长
and Sheriff Truman...
我不知道会是这位杜鲁门警长
I didn't know it would be this Sheriff Truman.
他说  他们会来找我
He said that they would come and ask me
然后问我一些关于库柏探员的事
about Special Agent Dale Cooper.
他跟我说这些时
He squeezed my shoulders
还捏着我的肩膀
when he told me this.
我还问他是什么事  但他...他
I tried to ask him what it was about, but he... he...
他不愿再多说什么
He wouldn't say any more.
他只说了
He just said,
"当他们来问你关于库柏探员的事时
"When they come to ask you about Agent Cooper,
你就把这东西给他们"
you give them this."
你们现在来了
And now you are here.
你的同事要喝咖啡吗
Would you fellas like some coffee?
-不  不用了  -不用了夫人
- No, no. - No, ma'am.
谢谢
Thank you.
那好
All right.
跟我来
Come with me.
这就是那把椅子
This is the chair.
我无法相信这一天到来了
I can't believe this day has come.
看这里
Watch right here.
博比  你父亲告诉我这事情时
Bobby, when your father told me this,
你还远不是
you were a very long way
现在这个样子
from where you are today.
不会怎么  他知道
Somehow, he knew
一切都会好的
that it would all turn out well.
他看到了你现在的生活
He saw this life for you.
你父亲从没有失去对你的希望
Your father never lost faith in you.
好吧  伙计们  我们来喝咖啡吧
Well, fellas, let's have that coffee.
-对  -对
- Yeah. - Yes.
-好吧  -绝对的
- Yeah? - You bet.
好的
Okay.
-好  -好的
- Yes. - Okay.
等待室
The waiting room.
就在我们后面
They're right behind us.
-诺克斯中尉  -长官
- Lieutenant Knox. - Sir.
麦克利
Macklay.
戴安
Diane.
我今天早上没心情看死尸
I'm not in the mood to see a dead body this morning.
我就在这儿等你们吧
I'll just wait for you guys here.
很抱歉  女士  你不能在这儿吸烟
I'm sorry, ma'am, you can't smoke here.
这他妈的是个停尸房
It's a fucking morgue!
这边走
This way.
死娘炮
Fuckin' Pansies.
晚饭时的谈话气氛很活跃
案子一开始是麦克利侦探负责的
Detective Macklay handled the case when it came in.
他会给你简要介绍背景的
He'll brief you on background.
威廉·黑斯廷斯那时候在和
William Hastings was having an affair
本地图书管理员露丝·达文波特搞婚外情
with the local librarian, Ruth Davenport.
现在  达文波特的头被发现在
Now, Davenport's head was found
布里格斯少校的无头身体上
atop the headless body of your Major Briggs.
我们刚一把黑斯廷斯抓起来
Once we took Hastings into custody,
他妻子在他们的房子里被杀
his wife was murdered in their house,
很显然是被他们的律师所杀
apparently by their lawyer,
一个叫乔治·邦思的男人
a man named George Bouncer,
现在也被抓起来了
who is now also in custody.
第二天
And the next day,
黑斯廷斯的秘书死在一场汽车爆炸中
Hastings's Secretary died in a car explosion.
第二季发生了什么
What happens in season two?
提前为艾伯特道歉
Apologies in advance for Albert.
这就是布里格斯少校
Well, this is your Major Briggs.
原来威廉·黑斯廷斯
It turns out that William Hastings,
在图书管理员露丝的帮助下
along with the help of Ruth the librarian,
调查并发表
was researching and publishing
一些关于其它维度的
some strange little blog
奇怪的博客
about some alternate dimension.
这是你们本地高中校长说的
This from the principal of your local high school.
他还是六年级的弹珠比赛冠军
Not to mention, marble champion of the sixth grade.
他什么时候把弹珠丢了
When did he lose his marbles?
狗抢走了他的猫眼弹珠
When the dog got his cat's eyes.
大约一周前  黑斯廷斯在博客最后
About one week ago, Hastings ended his blog entry
写了这么一句谜语
with this cryptic sentence:
今天我们终于进入了那个空间
"Today we finally entered what we call the Zone,
还遇到了少校
and we met the Major."
这是具四十几岁的男尸
This is the body of a man in his 40s.
对
Yes.
艾伯特
Albert.
我们好好想想
Let's think out loud.
布里格斯少校应该已经72岁了
Major Briggs would have been 72.
如你所知  我们以为他在25年前
As you know, we thought he died in a fire
就死于双峰镇外一座政府设施的
in that government facility outside Twin Peaks...
大火之中了
25 years ago.
那时他跟这个男人年龄差不多
About the age this man is now.
想想这个
Well, consider this.
库柏认识布里格斯
Cooper knew Briggs.
库柏在25年前就在布里格斯附近
Cooper was around Briggs 25 years ago,
现在  库柏就在这里出现了
and now, Cooper shows up in this neck of the woods.
在这里逍遥法外
On the loose in this neck of the woods.
没错
Right.
我在他胃里发现了这个
And I found this in his stomach.
它  它刻了字
It... it's inscribed.
上面写着  给道吉
It says, "To Dougie,
爱你  珍妮·E
love, Janey-E."
我们得跟这个威廉·黑斯廷斯谈谈
We need to speak with this William Hastings.
我不是你的脚
滚开
Go away!
露西
Hey, Lucy.
杜鲁门警长  我不在这儿
Sheriff Truman, I'm not here.
我正在午休时间
I'm on my lunch break.
警长
Oh, Sheriff. Oh.
会议室里不能吃饭  查德
No lunch in the conference room, Chad.
我知道  但是
I know, but...
你们经常在这儿喝咖啡吃面包圈啊
you guys have donuts and coffee in here all the time.
查德  带上你的午饭到午餐室去吃
Chad, take your lunch to the lunchroom.
好的
Sure thing.
没问题  警长
No problem, Sheriff.
很抱歉
Sorry.
下次不会了
Won't happen again.
能帮我开一下门吗
Could you get the door?
帮个忙
Little help here?
博比  打开窗户
Bobby, open the window.
好
Yeah.
没有接线
No seams.
没有开口
No openings.
这玩意要怎么开
How the heck are you supposed to open this thing?
也许哪里有个隐藏按钮
Maybe there's a hidden button somewhere.
我没看到什么隐藏按钮
I don't see any hidden button.
你在笑什么
What are you smiling at?
我不知道该怎么开
I know how to open that.
我爸爸有一点晚上带回家的
My dad brought one home one night.
你在逗我们吗  博比
You having fun with us, Bobby?
算是吧
Yeah, sort of.
你来
Go for it.
我们得回到外面去
We got to go back outside.
外面
Outside?
没错  我们得回到外面去
Yeah, we got to go back outside.
好吧
Okay.
怎么...
What the...
"杰克兔子的宫殿往东
"Two hundred fifty-three yards
253码
east of Jack Rabbit's Palace.
离开杰克兔子的宫殿前
Before leaving Jack Rabbit's Palace,
捧一把土放在
put some soil from that area
口袋里"
in your pocket."
两个日期
And two dates.
和一个时间
And a time.
同样的时间
Same time.
两点五十三分
2:53.
那是两天后
That's two days from now,
和三天后
and the day after.
杰克兔子的宫殿
Jack Rabbit's Palace?
我从来没听说过这个地方
I never heard of such a place.
他又来了
He did it again.
什么
What?
怎么回事  博比
What is it, Bobby?
我知道兔子杰克的宫殿在哪里
I know exactly where Jack Rabbit's Palace is.
我爸爸在我小时候
My dad, when I was a little kid,
带我去过这个地方
he took me to this place.
离我们的老警局很近
It was near where our station used to be.
是我们的奇迹之地
It was our make-believe world,
我们会在那里编故事
you know, where we made up stories.
是我叫那里杰克兔子的宫殿
I was the one who named it Jack Rabbit's Palace.
他预料到了这一切
He saw all this.
不管是怎么回事
Whatever this is.
我爸爸就是这样
That's my dad.
我们两天后去那里
We'll go up there two days from now,
你可以带路
and you can lead the way,
就想你爸爸想要的一样
just as your dad wanted.
等等
Wait a minute.
还有别的
There's something else.
库柏/库柏
"Cooper/cooper."
两个库柏
Two Coopers.
我们来陪你  戴安
We came out to join you, Diane,
艾伯特不舒服
while Albert's indisposed.
戈登
Gordon.
我们以前那个时候  经常一起抽烟
We used to smoke together, way back when.
你还记得吗
You remember?
当然了  戈登
Yeah, we sure did, Gordon.
当然了
We sure did.
谢谢你  戴安
Thanks, Diane.
不想抽完吗
You don's want to finish it off?
塔米
Tammy.
你好  黑斯廷斯先生
Hello, Mr. Hastings.
我是联调局的塔米·普雷斯顿探员
I'm Agent Tammy Preston of the FBI.
天啊  联调局
Oh, God, the FBI.
黑斯廷斯先生
Mr. Hastings,
我们的对话将被录像
I'm also recording our conversation.
好
Okay.
你能说出你的名字和年龄以供记录吗
Would you state your name and age for the record?
威廉·黑斯廷斯
William Hastings.
字幕
I'm 43.
黑斯廷斯先生  你是网上
Mr. Hastings, are you the author
一个叫《区域搜索》的
of an online journal or blog
文章作者或博客主吗
entitled The Search for the Zone?
是的
Uh-huh. Yes.
你都写些什么
What sort of things do you write about?
各种东西
Different things.
两周前
Approximately two weeks ago,
你是不是写道发现了
did you write an entry about encountering
所谓其他维度的入口
what you described as an alternate reality?
不同的维度
A different dimension.
是的  但这是真的
Yes, but it's real.
都是真的
It's all real.
你关注这类话题多久了  黑斯廷斯先生
How long have you been interested in this subject, Mr. Hastings?
很多年
Many years.
我...我读过很多
I do... I do a lot of reading.
但这一次  你写道你终于找到
But this time, you wrote that you actually found
并进入了这个地方
and entered such a place.
是的
Yes.
在这个地方
And that while in this place,
你写道  原文是
you wrote, and I quote,
"遇到了少校"
"We met the Major."
是的
Yeah. Yes.
露丝很擅长
You see, Ruth was very good at...
恢复隐藏记录
uncovering hidden records.
她说过如果我们在特定的时间
And she had indications that if we went to a certain place
去特定的地方
at a certain time,
就能进入那个维度
we would enter the dimension
就能和某个人取得联系
and make contact with a certain person.
我们就去了那里
And so we went there.
你们就在那里找到了上校
And that's where you found the Major.
他躲在那里
He was hiding there,
或者如他所说是"蛰伏"
or "Hibernating," As he said.
其他人可能...
And other people may...
可能会找到他
Were maybe gonna find him,
他想去其他地方
and he wanted to go to a different place,
所以他要我们给他找到数字
and so he asked us to get him numbers.
很重要的数字
Important numbers.
坐标
Coordinates.
我们在他要我们去的地方找到了
And we found them in the place he told us to go,
一个秘密军事基地
a secure military database.
那些坐标还在你这吗
Do you still have those coordinates?
不  在露丝那儿
No, Ruth had them.
她写在她的手上了
She wrote on her hand, though,
这样她就不会忘了
so that she wouldn't forget.
抱歉
Sorry.
然后呢  威廉
What happened then, William?
我们上周四把数字都给他了
We brought him back the numbers last Thursday.
然后发生了很可怕的事
And then something terrible happened.
那些人
These others...
那些人进来了
These others came in,
他们抓着我的脖子
and they grabbed me by the neck,
然后把我...把我推倒
and they pushed... They pushed me down.
他们说"你妻子叫什么"
They said, "What's your wife's name?
"你妻子叫什么"
"What's your wife's name?"
我说"菲莉斯"
"Phyllis," I said.
我没有杀露丝
I didn't kill Ruth.
我没有杀她
I didn't kill her.
你...你得相信我
You... you have to believe me.
我爱她
I loved her.
都是我的错
This is all my fault.
不该发生这种事的
It never should have happened.
威廉  我给你看的这六张照片里
William, are any of these six photographs I'm showing you
有你称为上校的人吗
the man you call the Major?
那就是上校
That's the Major.
在你指认为上校的人照片上画个圈
Draw a circle around the photo of the man you call the Major.
签字并署上日期
Sign and date it.
好的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
你能告诉我发生了什么吗
Can you tell me what happened?
我们把坐标给他
We gave him the numbers.
他开始飘起来
And he started to float up...
他说了一些词
and he said some words.
"库柏  库柏"
"Cooper. Cooper."
然后他就消失了
Right before his head disappeared.
好像根本就没存在过似的
It was something like no one has ever seen before.
我从来没见过这种事
I've never seen anything like it.
我...我从来没...我...
I... I've never... I've...
我从来没见过这种事
I've never read anything like it.
你都不知道  你不在场
You don't know. You weren't there.
那...他...
It was... he...
他...
He...
太美了...
It was beautiful.
然后露丝死了...
And then Ruth was dead.
太可怕了
It was so terrible,
我...我得抱着她
and I had... I had to hold her.
然后...然后我醒了
And then... and then I woke up,
我...我就在家里
and I was in... I was in my home.
我在家里
I was in my home.
上校杀了露丝吗
Did the Major kill Ruth?
不  那里有很多人
No, there were so many people there.
你要相信我
You have to believe me.
求你了  我没有杀露丝
Please, I didn't kill Ruth.
我爱她  我爱她
I loved her. I loved her.
我不知道我怎么了
I don't know what is happening to me.
你们为什么不能帮我  求你们了
Why can't you help me, please?
求你们了
Please.
我们一起很快乐
We were so happy together.
我们本来要一起去巴哈马
We were gonna go to the Bahamas.
我们本来要
We were gonna...
去潜水
scuba dive
在沙滩上喝鸡尾酒
and drink mixed drinks on the beach.
我们本来要一起日光浴
And we were gonna soak up the sun.
看美丽的夕阳
And look at the beautiful sunsets.
她说  她说  比尔  我们去吧
She said to me... She said, Bill, let't just go.
我们去吧
Let't just do it.
我们去巴哈马
Let's go to the Bahamas.
去潜水
Let's go scuba diving."
我想去潜水
I want to go scuba diving.
水果蛋糕  有人要吃吗
Fruitcake, anyone?
保安什么都没找到
Security couldn't find anything?
他们里里外外都找遍了
They checked everywhere.
这的声音似乎最大
It seems to be loudest here.
是...
It's, um...
这声音有点让人着迷
it's kind of a mesmerizing tone.
是
Yes.
修道院外的钟
The ring out of a monastery bell
也有这样的魔力
has the same quality.
或者...
Or the... hmm.
超脱尘世的
Otherworldly.
贝弗莉
Beverly.
我不能这么做
I can't do this.
我不知道为什么
I don't know why it is.
你是个好人  本
You are a good man, Ben.
你知道斑马又出来了吗
You know that zebra's out again?
好久不见了
Haven't seen you in a while.
我找到了另一份工作
I got another job.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
怎么了
What happened?
我被解雇了
I got fired.
那混蛋解雇了我
That fucker fired me.
真操蛋啊
That's fucked.
怎么了
How come?
估计是因为有几次去上班时嗑嗨了
I came in high a couple times, I guess.
估计
You guess?
是
Yeah.
操
Fuck.
我不记得了
I can't remember.
你知道我什么意思  有什么关系呢
You know what I mean. What's the big fucking deal?
我是说  我他妈工作了啊
I mean, I did the fucking work.
上汉堡能有什么问题
Like, how can you fuck up serving burgers,
你知道我什么意思吧
you know what I mean?
我起了些难受的疹子
I got some kind of wicked rash.
那你现在在哪工作
So where are you working now?
街对面
Across the fucking street,
上汉堡
serving burgers.
该死
Oh, shit.
你有看到那企鹅吗
Have you seen that penguin?
我...什么
Have I... what?
你知道的  企鹅
You know, the penguin.
是
Yep.
*我看着他们的脸*
*At their faces I'm looking*
*但我跟随着你的步伐*
*But your feet I'm following*
*在你带领的道路上*
*In soft steps on a path the way you lead*
*我不想失去自我*
*I don't want to lose myself*
*轻声耳语*
*It's a whisper*
*有趣的是*
*It's a funny thing*
*我们就像*
*We fold like icicles*
*纸架上的冰柱*
*On paper shelves*
*真可惜*
*It's a pity*
*这么出现*
*To appear this way*
*你在飞翔*
*You're flying*
*当你以外国人的角度*
*When your foreign eyes*
*追寻*
*Trace the heights*
*城市的高度*
*Of the city*
*我们呼吸着石头和云彩产生的蒸汽*
*Steaming with rocks and clouds we breathe*
-*狂野的天空*  -*对自己的身体震惊*
- *Violent skies* - *A shock to my own body*
*言语狂野  神圣嘹亮*
*Speech is wild alive sacred and sounding*
-*里里外外*  -*狂野*
- *From across and beyond* - *Wild*
*远远超过*
*Oh, far beyond*
*我不想失去自我*
*I don't want to lose myself*
*轻声耳语*
*It's a whisper*
*有趣的是*
*It's a funny thing*
*我们就像*
*We fold like icicles*
*纸架上的冰柱*
*On paper shelves*
*真可惜*
*It's a pity*
*这么出现*
*To appear this way*
*等等  等等  等一下*
*Hold, hold, hold on*
*我发誓我在哪见过*
*I swear I saw it somewhere*
*挥手  跋涉  一  二  三*
*Waving, wading, one, two, three*
*在那尾迹之上跟着的*
*Above the wakes that follow*
*等等  等等  等一下*
*Hold, hold, hold on*
*我发誓我在哪见过*
*I swear I saw it somewhere*
*挥手  跋涉  一  二  三*
*Waving, wading, one, two, three*
*在那尾迹之上跟着的*
*Above the wakes that follow*
-*我不想失去自我*  -*今晚我梦到*
- *I don't want to lose myself* - *Tonight I sleep to dream*
*一个呼唤我的地方*
*Of a place that's calling me*
-*轻声耳语*  -*永远只是个梦*
- *It's a whisper* - *It is always just a dream*
*有趣的是我仍忘不了我所看到的*
*It's a funny thing still I cannot forget what I have seen*
-*我们就像*  *我们呼吸着石头和云彩产生的蒸汽*
- *We fold like icicles* -*With rocks and clouds we breathe*
-*纸架上的冰柱*  -*对自己的身体震惊*
- *On paper shelves* - *A shock to my own body*
-*真可惜*  -*神圣嘹亮*
- *It's a pity* - *Alive sacred and sounding*
-*这么出现*  -*里里外外  远远超出*
- *To appear this way* - *From across and beyond, oh, far beyond*